<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2015 Dave Olsthoorn <dave.olsthoorn@gmail.com> -->
<component type="desktop">
 <id>qlcplus.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-3.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
 <name>Q Light Controller Plus</name>
 <summary>This is a software to control DMX or analog lighting systems</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="nl">Bestuur verlichting met DMX of analoge systemen</summary>
 <description>
  <p>
   QLC+ is free and cross-platform software to control DMX or analog lighting
   systems like moving heads, dimmers, scanners etc. This project is a fork of
   the great QLC project written by Heikki Junnila that aims to continue the
   development of QLC and to introduce new features. The primary goal is to
   bring QLC+ at the level of other commercial lighting control software.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="nl">
   QLC+ is gratis en cross-platform software voor het besturen van DMX of analoge
   verlichting systemen zoals moving heads, dimmers, scanners etc. Dit project is
   een verbetering van het grote QLC project geschreven door Heikki Junnila dat zich
   richt op de verder ontwikkeling van QLC en om nieuwe functies te introduceren. Het primaire
   doel is om QLC+ op het niveau van andere commerciële lichtregeling software te brengen.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   QLC+ è un software gratuito e multi piattaforma per controllare sistemi di illuminazione 
   DMX o analogici come teste mobili, dimmer, scanner, ecc. Questo progetto è un fork
   del magnifico progetto QLC scritto da Heikki Junnila, che mira a continuare lo sviluppo di
   QLC e a introdurre nuove funzionalità. L'obiettivo primario è di portare QLC+
   al livello di altri software commerciali per il controllo di illuminazione.
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>http://www.qlcplus.org/shots/qlcplus_fixtures.png</image>
   <caption>Fixtures panel</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
   <image>http://www.qlcplus.org/shots/qlcplus_virtualconsole2.png</image>
   <caption>Virtual Console</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
   <image>http://www.qlcplus.org/shots/qlcplus_multitrack2.png</image>
   <caption>Show Manager</caption>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">http://www.qlcplus.org/</url>
 <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/mcallegari/qlcplus/issues</url>
</component>
